<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentation on CMW的博客</title>
    <link>https://CheManWa.gitee.io/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Documentation on CMW的博客</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>@2020ChMW</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 23:55:41 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://CheManWa.gitee.io/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>目录</title>
      <link>https://CheManWa.gitee.io/docs/catalog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 23:55:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://CheManWa.gitee.io/docs/catalog/</guid>
      <description>[19335229]的软导作业索引页 课后作业  01-第一周作业-查找单词解释 02-第二周作业  实验与实践  01-我的MarkDown博客  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>数据结构作业2</title>
      <link>https://CheManWa.gitee.io/docs/homework02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 23:37:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://CheManWa.gitee.io/docs/homework02/</guid>
      <description>第二周作业 进制转换  1分12秒 = 72000 毫秒 (7A)13= (101)10 (7A)16= (122)10 (7A)16= (1111010)2= (172)8 (1011011)2= (133)8= (5B)16 (678)10= (1010100110)2= (1246)8 (111)2+ (101)2= (1100)2  解释关键词 Information Information can be thought of as the resolution of uncertainty
Positional notation Positional notation denotes usually the extension to any base of the Hindu–Arabic numeral system.
algorithm In mathematics and computer science, an algorithm is a finite sequence of well-defined, computer-implementable instructions, typically to solve a class of problems or to perform a computation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>数据结构作业1</title>
      <link>https://CheManWa.gitee.io/docs/homework01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 23:14:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://CheManWa.gitee.io/docs/homework01/</guid>
      <description>第一周作业-查找单词解释 computer A computer is a machine that can be instructed to carry out sequences of arithmetic or logical operations automatically via computer programming.
Computer science Computer science is the study of computation and information.
software software, is a collection of data or computer instructions that tell the computer how to work.
Software engineering Software engineering is the systematic application of engineering approaches to the development of software.
Alan Mathison Turing Alan Mathison Turing (23 June 1912 – 7 June 1954) was an English mathematician, computer scientist, logician, cryptanalyst, philosopher, and theoretical biologist.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>